I have new latex outfits to show you because I got outfits from Inner Sanctum, a really well-renowned and high-quality latex label from Hamburg.
Sneak peek leopard printed latex.
And I visited them a few weeks ago in Hamburg and took these with me to show them to you.
I'm going to send them back so you can actually order these afterwards or get yours made to measure or customized.
and I already visited the showroom some years ago which I recorded for YouTube.
You can see that here. But now I'm going to start right away with the first outfit.
First outfit and it's this really cute combination of skater skirt and neck
holder top. It's giving me cheerleader vibes to be honest. I do need some pom-poms
and I can jump around and because it's just so cute really cute this is from
the latest collection the saint and sinner collection and I have been on the
catwalk for inner sanctum at GFB last year where they presented this
collection and I've worn an incredible cat suit I can show you some pictures so
this is from the same collection and I think it's a really beginner friendly
outfit so to say so if you're looking to get into latex or get your girlfriend into latex
this skater skirt is super easy to dress and the neck holder top which has a snap button here in
the neck is also super easy to dress so I can definitely recommend this if you want to try out
latex or if you're just looking for something cute for summer that is not too much latex or
like party outfit, playful one. Yeah the belt is detachable so it's an additional
item here which matches great with the top the black and white theme again.
And I just feel so cute. I do love this cut off collar here the high neck collar. I think I'm
I'm going to change into the next outfit, which is this lottery set in military style.
Second outfit is this really cute, again cute, military underwear combination.
So we have a bra and a panty in olive green I'd say and transparent.
It's also like a greenish transparent.
gives a bit military or also maybe circus vibes here with the design and I
can tell you since I make latex clothing myself that this is like a really really
work intensive outfit there went a lot of work into this with all the details
all the buttons you have to reinforce the latex with fabric you have to punch
all the holes you have to cut all the trims and yeah just assemble everything
thing also with the straps here and the metal hardware the straps are size
adjustable so this is really awesome and not something you find in normal latex
clothing so as I said InnoSectum is really such a high quality brand I've
known them for ages their first latex brand I've been on the catwalk for in
2016 so first fashion show in the alternative fashion scene I work for
them. Julia and Max are such awesome people. Yeah, if you're ever in Hamburg, stop by or have a look
at their homepage. They make all outfits, major, major. You can also tell them what kind of outfit
you like and they design it for you. So it's really awesome service and they're awesome people too.
I decided to pair the green of this set with the red boots for contrast and I think it works
really great. I'm missing some maybe red gloves for example but yeah I really
like the outfit. Also the impression of the transparent parts here. Really really nice. I really enjoyed this one.
As for the last outfit, I'm going to unpack this really heavy and sturdy corset.
And I have to get changed now.
Here it is.
Leopard print, or not print, but latex pattern.
And I've never worn something with leopard patterns, especially not in latex,
because I always thought it's tacky.
But I think in this combination with this, like, slight amount of leopard, it does work.
And I do like it, especially the contrast to the black, because overall the outfit is black.
So when I turn around it's just black which works in the favor of the pattern I'd say.
I paired it with the pencil skirt and that pencil skirt is super tight so you can see when I'm walking that there is not much room for like big steps.
So of course latex is stretchy but only to a certain extent.
We also have these hip boning here. Flexible, but the latex is really thick, so the whole part here is really sturdy.
And the corset has multiple layers, so it's a really heavy and firm piece, which also really works wonders for the figure.
So I could really lace that waist down.
usually I wear size small for InnoSanctum latex but this corset was actually made for someone else
for someone else's measurements and when I visited Julia a few weeks ago we said let's just try it
if it fits me and it does which is super cool because I also like the cups here I was like I
want to try something with cups because they always fit me so good their cups so I don't know
why but in a sanctum latex always has a perfect fit for me again we have a lot of details and a
lot of work that went into this with all the buckles here and the holes which you have to
punch and then rivet and yeah all the layers all the trims so this is really great craftsmanship
as well I put some gloves on because I think that's I don't know somehow makes
it more complete you could also wear it with boots for example yeah I think this
is really an eye-catcher piece I love it if I had to rank the outfits I don't
know I think they're so different and so many different styles would like the
cheerleader one, the military one and now this. I cannot really make a ranking of
these outfits. I'm sorry I just love them all. But you can tell me which one was
your favorite in the comments and if you're interested to see more of InnoCentrum
check out their social media profiles, their webshop or visit them in Hamburg
and check out my social media profiles, leave a thumbs up. I will post some more
pictures on my Patreon probably and yeah hope you had fun with this video I will
see you in the next one have a nice day bye